{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "The name of Junko Enoshima&#039;s imposter at the beginning of Danganronpa: Trigger Happy Havoc is?",
      "correct_answer": "Mukuro Ikusaba",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ryota Mitarai",
        "Ultimate Imposter",
        "Komaru Naegi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Vehicles",
      "question": "Which car tire manufacturer is famous for its &quot;Eagle&quot; brand of tires, and is the official tire supplier of NASCAR?",
      "correct_answer": "Goodyear",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pirelli",
        "Bridgestone",
        "Michelin"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What year did Skoal, a smokeless Tobacco company, release their first line of Pouches, known as &quot;Skoal Bandits&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "1983",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1934",
        "1984",
        "1822"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level &quot;Hidden Palace Zone&quot; was later reused in the iOS port of the game. ",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "How many aces can be shot down through the entirety of &quot;Ace Combat Zero: The Belkan War&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "169",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "100",
        "132",
        "245"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Books",
      "question": "What was the pen name of novelist, Mary Ann Evans?",
      "correct_answer": "George Eliot",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "George Orwell",
        "George Bernard Shaw",
        "George Saunders"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In &quot;One Piece&quot;, who confirms the existence of the legendary treasure, One Piece?",
      "correct_answer": "Edward &quot;Whitebeard&quot; Newgate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Former Marine Fleet Admiral Sengoku",
        "Pirate King Gol D Roger",
        "Silvers Rayleigh"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "What is the default alias that Princess Garnet goes by in Final Fantasy IX?",
      "correct_answer": "Dagger",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dirk",
        "Garnet",
        "Quina"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Television",
      "question": "In the Sci-Fi television show Doctor Who, who plays the Tenth Doctor?",
      "correct_answer": "David Tennant",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "William Hartnell",
        "Peter Capaldi",
        "Peter Davison"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Joseph Stalin&#039;s real name was Ioseb Bessarionis dze Dzugashvili.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "The Dice Tower network of board game podcasts and videos is run by which individual?",
      "correct_answer": "Tom Vasel",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jason LeVine",
        "Borth Sampson",
        "Uncle Pennybags"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the &quot;Ace Attorney&quot; series, what is the relationship between Apollo Justice and Trucy Wright?",
      "correct_answer": "They&#039;re half-siblings",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "They&#039;re co-workers",
        "They&#039;re friends",
        "They&#039;re both attorneys"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the second-largest city in Lithuania?",
      "correct_answer": "Kaunas",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Panevėžys",
        "Vilnius",
        "Klaipėda"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The mobile game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was released in what year? ",
      "correct_answer": "2011",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2012",
        "2009",
        "2014"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
      "question": "Which of these bones is hardest to break?",
      "correct_answer": "Femur",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cranium",
        "Humerus",
        "Tibia"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;The Binding of Isaac&quot;, what is the name of the final boss that you fight in The Void?",
      "correct_answer": "Delirium",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mega Satan",
        "Hush",
        "The Lamb"
      ]
    }
  ]
}